♫ Suddenly you said you wanted to break up completely ♫
♫ فجأة قلت أنك تريد الانفصال تماما ♫
♫ But last night, you still kissed me goodbye ♫
♫ لكن الليلة الماضية، مازلت تقبلني وداعًا ♫
♫ And then you'd spend all night planning the future for the two of us ♫
♫ ومن ثم تقضي الليل كله في التخطيط لمستقبلنا نحن الاثنين ♫
♫  I said, "Okay, we'll return to our parents and not speak nonsense"  ♫
♫ قلت، "حسنًا، سنعود إلى والدينا ولن نتحدث بالهراء" ♫
♫  You've dumped me, and it's not easy to be single again  ♫
♫ لقد هجرتني، وليس من السهل أن أعود أعزباً مرة أخرى ♫
♫ Once again, my love life has infinite opportunities ♫
♫ مرة أخرى، حياتي العاطفية لديها فرص لا حصر لها ♫
♫ Everything is moving too fast, it's hard to accept  ♫
♫ كل شيء يتحرك بسرعة كبيرة، ومن الصعب قبوله ♫
♫  I hid my inexplicable excitement with a wry smile ♫
♫ أخفيت حماستي التي لا يمكن تفسيرها بابتسامة ساخرة ♫
♫ It's hard to become single once again ♫
♫ من الصعب أن تصبح عازباً مرة أخرى ♫
♫ Once again, my love life has infinite opportunities ♫
♫ مرة أخرى، حياتي العاطفية لديها فرص لا حصر لها ♫
♫ Our love has been engraved deep in my heart ♫
♫ حبنا محفور بعمق في قلبي ♫
♫ In the end, we're no longer together ♫
♫ في النهاية، لم نعد معًا ♫
♫ In the end, we've become a pair of strangers ♫
♫ في النهاية، أصبحنا زوجًا من الغرباء ♫
[Fall In Love]
[اقع في الحب]
[Episode 13]
[الحلقة 13]
Ai Xin, are you sure you want to be together with a brat like him?
آي شين، هل أنت متأكد من أنك تريد أن تكون مع طفل شقي مثله؟
Do you think he's capable enough to marry you?
هل تعتقدين أنه قادر بما فيه الكفاية على الزواج منك؟
Marry me, Senior Sister.
تزوجيني يا أختي الكبرى.
Drop the act.
إسقاط الفعل.
Are you making fun of me?
هل تسخر مني؟
Yes.
نعم.
I don't buy it.
أنا لا أشتريه.
Do you want to be with this brat?
هل تريد أن تكون مع هذا الشقي؟
Enough with the names! Do you think I'm a brat?
كفى بالأسماء! هل تعتقد أنني شقي؟
Do you believe it now?
هل تصدق ذلك الآن؟
You're the one who abandoned her.
أنت الذي تخليت عنها.
Can you leave with some dignity?
هل يمكنك الرحيل ببعض الكرامة؟
You're going after my leftover. Where's your dignity?
أنت تسعى وراء بقاياي. أين كرامتك؟
- What... - Stop!
- ماذا... - توقف!
Stop fighting.
توقف عن القتال.
Get up.
استيقظ.
I knew it.
كنت أعرف.
You still care about me.
أنت لا تزال تهتم بي.
If you punch his face, he can prove it with a check-up,
إذا لكمته على وجهه، يمكنه إثبات ذلك بإجراء فحص طبي،
but like this, he can't prove anything.
لكن بهذه الطريقة، لا يستطيع إثبات أي شيء.
After all these years with him, I can't believe I'd done that to him.
بعد كل هذه السنوات معه، لا أستطيع أن أصدق أنني فعلت ذلك به.
Since we've said it, he should believe you are my boyfriend now.
بما أننا قلنا ذلك، عليه أن يصدق أنك صديقي الآن.
So did you do everything just to put on an act with Ma Shixian?
إذًا هل فعلت كل شيء لتمثل مع ما شيكسيان؟
Sorry. Did I scare you?
آسف. هل أخافتك؟
How can you write it off so easily?
كيف يمكنك شطبها بهذه السهولة؟
What are you trying to say?
ماذا تحاول أن تقول؟
Don't you have any feelings for me at all?
ليس لديك أي مشاعر تجاهي على الإطلاق؟
I don't know.
لا أعرف.
Enough!
كافٍ!
♫  If you were by my side,  ♫
♫ لو كنت بجانبي، ♫
♫  No matter how many promises we've broken  ♫
♫ بغض النظر عن عدد الوعود التي نكثناها ♫
♫  There's nothing I'm not willing to do  ♫
♫ لا يوجد شيء لست على استعداد لفعله ♫
♫  Just to have a simple and ordinary life with you  ♫
♫ فقط لأحظى بحياة بسيطة وعادية معك ♫
♫  If you were by my side,  ♫
♫ لو كنت بجانبي، ♫
♫  All my regrets will be blown away by the wind  ♫
♫ كل ما أشعر به من ندم سوف تتطايره الريح ♫
[Senior Director Fu]
[المدير الأول فو]
♫  I only want you to be with me every second, every minute  ♫
♫ أريدك فقط أن تكون معي في كل ثانية، كل دقيقة ♫
Understood.
مفهوم.
Junior Brother, aren't you busy?
الأخ الأصغر، ألست مشغولاً؟
You should go home.
يجب عليك العودة إلى المنزل.
No, I have all the time in the world.
لا، لدي كل الوقت في العالم.
Don't you believe me?
ألا تصدقني؟
Don't do this to me.
لا تفعل هذا بي.
This isn't who you are.
هذا ليس من أنت.
Who was on the phone just now?
من كان على الهاتف للتو؟
Jian Bufan!
جيان بوفان!
We can only be friends.
يمكننا أن نكون أصدقاء فقط.
Senior Sister.
الأخت الكبرى.
I know that's not what you mean.
أعلم أن هذا ليس ما تقصده.
What happened? Please tell me.
ماذا حدث؟ من فضلك قل لي.
Senior Sister?
الأخت الكبرى؟
Ai Xin?
آي شين؟
I'm sorry.
أنا آسف.
Don't get upset, Senior Sister.
لا تنزعجي يا أختي الكبرى
Director Fu, I'm a little under the weather. I'd like to ask for a few days off.
أيها المدير فو، أنا متأثر قليلاً بالطقس. أود أن أطلب إجازة لبضعة أيام.
Sure.
بالتأكيد.
How do I look?
كيف أبدو؟
It's just a launch event. Why are you wearing a wedding dress?
إنه مجرد حدث إطلاق. لماذا ترتدين فستان الزفاف؟
It's been confirmed that the launch event will be carried out as a wedding.
لقد تم التأكيد على أن حفل الإطلاق سيتم كحفل زفاف.
As Helai Jewelry's representative, I'll marry you who belongs to Fu Group.
كممثل لمجوهرات هيلاي، سأتزوجك من تنتمي إلى مجموعة فو.
Sure.
بالتأكيد.
Try it on. I have other matters to tend to.
جربه. لدي أمور أخرى يجب أن أهتم بها.
Miss He, this wedding dress is our store's gem.
آنسة هي، فستان الزفاف هذا هو جوهرة متجرنا.
You picked well. Not many people get to wear it.
لقد أحسنت الاختيار. لا يستطيع الكثير من الناس ارتدائه.
- I'll buy this dress. Don't put it on display again. - Okay.
- سأشتري هذا اللباس. لا تعرضه للعرض مرة أخرى. - تمام.
Zeyi. Thanks.
زيي. شكرًا.
Don't get it wrong. This isn't for you.
لا تفهم الأمر بشكل خاطئ. هذا ليس لك.
Then whom is it for?
ثم لمن؟
Miss Jing, this way, please.
آنسة جينغ، من هنا، من فضلك.
Zhixia.
زيكسيا.
What are the odds? I'm here to collect the wedding dress.
ما هي الاحتمالات؟ أنا هنا لجمع فستان الزفاف.
I heard about what happened. Congratulations on the engagement.
سمعت عما حدث. مبروك على الخطوبة.
Do you think I'm marrying someone else?
هل تعتقدين أنني سأتزوج بشخص آخر؟
I saw it with my own eyes.
رأيت ذلك بأم عيني.
Yes. You're right.
نعم. أنت على حق.
I'm getting engaged to her next week. Don't be late.
سأخطبها الأسبوع المقبل. لا تتأخر.
If you still need a venue, you may consider Aizhe Hotel. I'll provide you with the best services.
إذا كنت لا تزال بحاجة إلى مكان، فيمكنك التفكير في فندق Aizhe. سأقدم لك أفضل الخدمات.
That sounds great, Zeyi.
هذا يبدو عظيما، زيي.
We'll have the reception at Aizhe Hotel.
سيكون لدينا حفل استقبال في فندق Aizhe.
Then it's settled. I didn't think a visit to this store would bring me a valued customer.
ثم تمت تسويتها. لم أكن أعتقد أن زيارة هذا المتجر ستجلب لي عميلاً مهمًا.
Take your time. I should get going.
خذ وقتك. يجب أن أذهب.
Pack this wedding dress up.
احزمي فستان الزفاف هذا.
Yes.
نعم.
Jing Zhixia...
جينغ زيكسيا ...
[Aizhe Hotel]
[فندق آيزهي]
[New bookings]
[الحجوزات الجديدة]
This is a big order.
هذا أمر كبير.
I'd be a fool for not accepting it.
سأكون أحمق لعدم قبول ذلك.
[He Bei'er requires Director Jing Zhixia to be the person in charge.]
[يطلب He Bei'er أن يكون المدير Jing Zhixia هو الشخص المسؤول.]
No, I can't choose money over Zhixia's feelings.
لا، لا أستطيع اختيار المال على حساب مشاعر زيكسيا.
[Booking accepted]
[تم قبول الحجز]
That's a big order. Why wouldn't you accept it?
هذا أمر كبير. لماذا لا تقبل ذلك؟
My Zhixia is all grown up. She understands the bigger picture.
لقد كبرت Zhixia الخاصة بي. إنها تفهم الصورة الأكبر.
I learned from the best, my uncle.
لقد تعلمت من الأفضل يا عمي.
Of course.
بالطبع.
During the event, try avoiding them. I'll send someone else as our liaison.
أثناء الحدث، حاول تجنبهم. سأرسل شخصًا آخر ليكون مسؤول الاتصال لدينا.
No, they are doing this to provoke me.
لا، إنهم يفعلون هذا لاستفزازي.
I feel no guilt. Why should I run away?
لا أشعر بالذنب. لماذا يجب أن أهرب؟
I believe in you. Look, show off your professionalism to the wretched couple.
إنني أ ثق بك. أنظر، أظهر احترافك للزوجين البائسين.
Consider the couple as complete strangers.
اعتبر الزوجين غرباء تمامًا.
Hello, Miss He. I am Jing Zhixia. I'm the person in charge of the Aizhe Hotel.
مرحباً يا آنسة هو. أنا جينغ زيكسيا. أنا الشخص المسؤول عن فندق Aizhe.
I'm younger than you. Just address me as Bei'er, Sister Zhixia.
أنا أصغر منك. فقط خاطبيني باسم Bei'er، الأخت Zhixia.
Right. I went through the files. This is a corporate banquet.
يمين. ذهبت من خلال الملفات. هذه مأدبة للشركات.
You may check the event schedule.
يمكنك التحقق من الجدول الزمني للحدث.
For a mere strategical corporate launch event,
مجرد حدث إطلاق استراتيجي للشركة،
the lighting ceremony seems outstanding. However...
يبدو حفل الإضاءة رائعًا. لكن...
it's not just about Helai Jewelry and the Fu Group.
الأمر لا يتعلق فقط بمجوهرات هيلاي ومجموعة فو.
My engagement with Zeyi will be announced during the event.
سيتم الإعلان عن خطوبتي مع Zeyi خلال الحدث.
Perhaps, we could turn it into an engagement party.
ربما يمكننا تحويلها إلى حفلة خطوبة.
I love befriending smart people like you, Sister Zhixia.
أحب مصادقة الأشخاص الأذكياء مثلك، أخت زيكسيا.
I'll replace the lighting ceremony with champagne serving.
سأستبدل حفل الإضاءة بتقديم الشمبانيا.
That'd be great.
سيكون ذلك رائعًا.
However, the champagne must be alcohol-free.
ومع ذلك، يجب أن تكون الشمبانيا خالية من الكحول.
- I want a nonslip mat on the path I walk. - Okay.
- أريد حصيرة غير قابلة للانزلاق على الطريق الذي أمشي فيه. - تمام.
After all, it's best to be cautious now that I'm pregnant.
ففي النهاية، من الأفضل أن أكون حذرة الآن بعد أن أصبحت حاملاً.
Congratulations. That's a double delight.
تهانينا. هذه فرحة مزدوجة.
From what I know, you were close with Zeyi.
مما أعرفه أنك كنت قريبًا من زيي.
I was worried you'd consider it awkward.
كنت قلقة من أنك قد تعتبر الأمر محرجًا.
Why would I do this?
لماذا أفعل هذا؟
That's great. If that's the case, I have a small favor to ask.
هذا عظيم. إذا كان الأمر كذلك، لدي خدمة صغيرة لأطلبها.
I need your help with something.
أحتاج مساعدتك في شيء ما.
I'll do my best to fulfill the customer's requests.
سأبذل قصارى جهدي لتلبية طلبات العميل.
I need your help during the engagement party.
أحتاج لمساعدتكم خلال حفل الخطوبة.
What is it?
ما هذا؟
Could you deliver the engagement rings to me?
هل يمكنك تسليم خواتم الخطبة لي؟
I don't think we are close enough for me to deliver the rings to you.
لا أعتقد أننا قريبون بما فيه الكفاية بالنسبة لي لتسليم الخواتم إليك.
Who says we must be close to do that?
من يقول أننا يجب أن نكون قريبين للقيام بذلك؟
I need someone for the event flow.
أحتاج إلى شخص ما لتدفق الحدث.
But the exchange of rings is pivotal in this partnership,
لكن تبادل الخواتم أمر محوري في هذه الشراكة،
it's best to leave it to someone as reliable as you.
فمن الأفضل أن تترك الأمر لشخص موثوق به مثلك.
- I think... - Of course, I know you were in a relationship with Zeyi.
- أعتقد... - بالطبع، أعلم أنك كنت على علاقة مع Zeyi.
If you mind, I'll get someone else.
إذا كنت تمانع، سأحضر شخصًا آخر.
I don't mind at all.
لا أمانع على الإطلاق.
I'll leave it to you, then, Sister Zhixia.
سأترك الأمر لك إذن يا أخت زيكسيا.
- Zeyi? - Why are you here?
- زيي؟ - لماذا أنت هنا؟
I knew you'd be busy, so I went to Aizhe Hotel and checked the event's schedule.
كنت أعرف أنك ستكون مشغولاً، لذلك ذهبت إلى فندق Aizhe وتحققت من جدول الحدث.
You can decide on the matter.
يمكنك اتخاذ قرار بشأن هذه المسألة.
Miss Jing is a very capable person.
الآنسة جينغ شخص قادر جدًا.
She sent me the new schedule the same day after our discussion.
لقد أرسلت لي الجدول الجديد في نفس اليوم بعد مناقشتنا.
[Schedule of Launch Event]
[الجدول الزمني لحدث الإطلاق]
[Introducing the engaged couple]
[التعريف بالزوجين المخطوبين]
Ring exchange during the launch event?
تبادل الخاتم أثناء حدث الإطلاق؟
- Jing Zhixia arranged this? - Yes.
- جينغ Zhixia رتبت هذا؟ - نعم.
Miss Jing suggested that we carry it out as an engagement party.
اقترحت الآنسة جينغ أن نقيمها كحفلة خطوبة.
She sent her regards, saying it was a double delight.
أرسلت تحياتها قائلة إنها كانت فرحة مضاعفة.
Jing Zhixia, do you really want me to marry another woman?
جينغ زيكسيا، هل تريد حقًا أن أتزوج امرأة أخرى؟
As long as you like it. We'll proceed with her arrangement.
طالما كنت ترغب في ذلك. سنواصل ترتيباتها.
Yes.
نعم.
Ladies and gentlemen, the event will soon begin.
سيداتي وسادتي، سيبدأ الحدث قريبًا.
We'll be ready in a moment. Thank you.
سنكون جاهزين في لحظة. شكرًا لك.
Zeyi is such an outstanding young man.
Zeyi هو مثل هذا الشاب المتميز.
I can see now why Bei'er always talks about him.
أستطيع أن أرى الآن لماذا يتحدث بيير عنه دائمًا.
Are you really going to let Fu Zeyi get engaged to He Bei'er?
هل ستسمح حقًا لـ Fu Zeyi بالمشاركة مع He Bei'er؟
He Bei'er is clearly not a person who is easy to deal with.
من الواضح أن He Bei'er ليس شخصًا يسهل التعامل معه.
Since Jing Zhixia is here today,
بما أن جينغ زيكسيا موجود هنا اليوم،
we should expect a great show.
يجب أن نتوقع عرضًا رائعًا.
Thank you for attending the Fu and He family's strategic partnership banquet.
شكرًا لك على حضور مأدبة الشراكة الإستراتيجية لعائلة Fu and He.
Before we begin, let's welcome the stars of our event.
قبل أن نبدأ، دعونا نرحب بنجوم هذا الحدث.
A round of applause for them.
جولة من التصفيق لهم.
This partnership has become the perfect role model for the finance industry.
أصبحت هذه الشراكة نموذجًا مثاليًا لصناعة التمويل.
As we can see, the couple is a match made in heaven.
كما نرى، فإن الزوجين متطابقان في الجنة.
And the most important part is coming up next.
والجزء الأكثر أهمية هو القادم.
We also have a more surprising announcement for everyone.
لدينا أيضًا إعلان أكثر إثارة للدهشة للجميع.
Before we start, I'd like to invite a friend to the stage.
قبل أن نبدأ، أود أن أدعو صديقًا إلى المسرح.
Sister Zhixia.
الأخت زيكسيا.
Let's welcome Miss Zhixia.
دعونا نرحب بالآنسة Zhixia.
During my years abroad, I didn't have many friends,
خلال السنوات التي أمضيتها في الخارج، لم يكن لدي الكثير من الأصدقاء،
but Zhixia and I got along very well.
لكن أنا و Zhixia كنا على علاقة جيدة جدًا.
I'd like to invite you as a friend to witness the moment of our life.
أود أن أدعوك كصديق لتشهد لحظة من حياتنا.
Okay. Our staff member will now deliver the rings.
تمام. سيقوم موظفنا الآن بتسليم الحلقات.
Miss Zhixia, please deliver the rings to the couple.
آنسة زيكسيا، من فضلك قم بتسليم الخواتم للزوجين.
♫  The first heartbeat feeling is fearless to what may come forever  ♫
♫ أول شعور بنبض القلب هو عدم الخوف مما قد يأتي إلى الأبد ♫
♫  Some of the simplest words can be used to encourage each other  ♫
♫ يمكن استخدام بعض أبسط الكلمات لتشجيع بعضنا البعض ♫
♫  Our first love's ending is not beautiful at all  ♫
♫ نهاية حبنا الأول ليست جميلة على الإطلاق ♫
♫  The sorrow for the passing years is haunting  ♫
♫ الحزن على السنوات الماضية يطاردني ♫
♫  So I can only yearn and get drunk  ♫
♫ لذلك لا أستطيع إلا أن أشتاق وأسكر ♫
♫  At the end of our first love, regret is the most beautiful  ♫
♫ في نهاية حبنا الأول، الندم هو الأجمل ♫
♫  It's a story only my heart can appreciate  ♫
♫ إنها قصة لا يقدرها إلا قلبي ♫
♫  Memories can be painful yet silent and at ease when I reminisce  ♫
♫ يمكن أن تكون الذكريات مؤلمة ولكنها صامتة وتشعر بالراحة عندما أتذكرها ♫
My engagement with Zeyi will be announced during the banquet.
سيتم الإعلان عن خطوبتي مع Zeyi خلال المأدبة.
♫  Our first love's ending is not beautiful at all  ♫
♫ نهاية حبنا الأول ليست جميلة على الإطلاق ♫
The lady will now put the ring on for the gentleman.
ستقوم السيدة الآن بوضع الخاتم للرجل.
It's your turn now, Zeyi.
حان دورك الآن، زيي.
♫  At the end of our first love, regret is the most beautiful  ♫
♫ في نهاية حبنا الأول، الندم هو الأجمل ♫
♫  It's a story only my heart can appreciate  ♫
♫ إنها قصة لا يقدرها إلا قلبي ♫
♫  Memories can be painful yet silent and at ease when I reminisce  ♫
♫ يمكن أن تكون الذكريات مؤلمة ولكنها صامتة وتشعر بالراحة عندما أتذكرها ♫
The ring exchange has been completed.
تم الانتهاء من تبادل الخاتم.
Next, let's welcome with a round of applause the chairmen of both companies.
بعد ذلك، دعونا نرحب برئيسي الشركتين بجولة من التصفيق.
- Good.
- جيد. - جيد.
I should go now.
يجب أن أذهب الآن.
What's the hurry, Sister Zhixia?
ما هو الاستعجال يا أخت Zhixia؟
This is a partnership event and your engagement party.
هذا حدث شراكة وحفلة خطوبتك.
Why would you want me here?
لماذا تريدني هنا؟
I'd like to thank everyone present.
أود أن أشكر جميع الحاضرين.
I must express my thanks to the person in charge of this event.
ويجب أن أتقدم بالشكر إلى الشخص المسؤول عن هذا الحدث.
Miss Jing Zhixia.
الآنسة جينغ زيكسيا.
Sister Zhixia, thank you.
الأخت زيكسيا، شكرا لك.
We only have this wonderful event because of your effort.
ليس لدينا هذا الحدث الرائع إلا بفضل مجهودكم.
- Calm down. - You have my thanks.
- اهدأ. - لك شكري.
I should go now.
يجب أن أذهب الآن.
Did I say you could leave?
هل قلت أنه يمكنك المغادرة؟
By the way, Sister Zhixia is currently single.
بالمناسبة، الأخت Zhixia عازبة حاليا.
This is the chance for all you single gentlemen out there.
هذه هي الفرصة لكم جميعا أيها السادة العزاب هناك.
Next...
التالي...
- What is happening? - What's the matter?
- ماذا يحدث؟ - ماذا جرى؟
The lights are off.
الأضواء مطفأة.
♫  If you were by my side  ♫
♫ لو كنت بجانبي ♫
♫  No matter how many promises we've broken  ♫
♫ بغض النظر عن عدد الوعود التي نكثناها ♫
♫  There's nothing I'm not willing to do  ♫
♫ لا يوجد شيء لست على استعداد لفعله ♫
♫  in order to have a simple and ordinary life with you  ♫
♫ لكي أحظى بحياة بسيطة وعادية معك ♫
♫  If you were by my side  ♫
♫ لو كنت بجانبي ♫
♫  All my regrets will be blown away by the wind  ♫
♫ كل ما أشعر به من ندم سوف تتطايره الريح ♫
♫  I only want you to be with me every second, every minute  ♫
♫ أريدك فقط أن تكون معي في كل ثانية، كل دقيقة ♫
So Director Fu ordered me to turn off the lights in order for him to escape?
إذن أمرني المدير فو بإطفاء الأضواء حتى يهرب؟
Thank you, Miss He Bei'er and Mr. Fu Zeyi. They represent Helai Jewelry and the Fu Group.
شكرًا لك، الآنسة هي بيير والسيد فو زيي. إنهم يمثلون مجوهرات Helai ومجموعة Fu.
Old Fu? What happened?
فو القديم؟ ماذا حدث؟
Thanks to them, we have this symbolic and meaningful ring exchange.
وبفضلهم، حصلنا على هذا التبادل الرمزي والهادف.
What's happening here?
ماذا يحدث هنا؟
So it's just a business partnership.
لذا فهي مجرد شراكة تجارية.
The engagement was just a publicity stunt.
كانت المشاركة مجرد حيلة دعائية.
Trouble is brewing.
المشكلة تختمر.
Let me go!
دعني أذهب!
Zhixia.
زيكسيا.
Don't call me that. We're not that close!
لا تدعوني بذلك. نحن لسنا قريبين إلى هذا الحد!
I'm not interested in anything about you.
أنا لست مهتمة بأي شيء عنك.
I don't want anything to do with you either.
لا أريد أن أفعل أي شيء معك أيضًا.
I'm sorry.
أنا آسف.
You should get back there.
يجب عليك العودة إلى هناك.
I dragged you out, so there is no way I'm going back in.
لقد سحبتك للخارج، لذلك ليس هناك طريقة للعودة مرة أخرى.
You're right. I tried,
أنت على حق. حاولت،
but I can't forget about you.
لكن لا أستطيع أن أنساك.
You should know everything in there was just a show.
يجب أن تعلم أن كل شيء كان هناك مجرد عرض.
Why should I care what it is?
لماذا يجب أن أهتم بما هو؟
- Don't you understand what I mean? - I don't get it.
- ألا تفهم ما أقصده؟ - انا لم احصل عليها.
I don't want to.
لا أريد أن.
Fine.
بخير.
If you insist, let me make it clear to you.
إذا كنت تصر، اسمحوا لي أن أوضح لك.
Jing Zhixia.
جينغ زيكسيا.
I've done everything just to receive your answer.
لقد فعلت كل شيء فقط لتلقي إجابتك.
My answer? I have an answer for you right now.
إجابتي؟ لدي إجابة لك الآن.
I don't want to see you again.
لا أريد أن أراك مرة أخرى.
Stay away from me.
ابتعد عني.
Zhixia...
زيكسيا...
[Aizhe Hotel]
[فندق آيزهي]
Eldest Brother, the launch event was a success. We've dealt with the media,
أيها الأخ الأكبر، لقد كان حفل الإطلاق ناجحًا. لقد تعاملنا مع وسائل الإعلام،
but the He family seemed upset when they left.
لكن عائلة هي بدت مستاءة عندما غادروا.
He Yesheng seemed very upset.
بدا هو Yesheng مستاء للغاية.
I'm worried our partnership might face some obstacles.
أشعر بالقلق من أن شراكتنا قد تواجه بعض العقبات.
Let's wait and see. The He family needs time to calm down.
دعونا ننتظر ونرى. تحتاج عائلة هو إلى وقت لتهدأ.
So what about Zeyi?
فماذا عن زيي؟
Enough with that insolent son!
كفى من هذا الابن الوقح!
He can do whatever he wants.
يمكنه أن يفعل ما يريد.
[Aizhe Hotel]
[فندق آيزهي]
Director Fu, are you here for Miss Jing?
المدير فو، هل أنت هنا من أجل الآنسة جينغ؟
She had already gone out.
لقد خرجت بالفعل.
Hello?
مرحبًا؟
I apologized to you. Why are you still avoiding me?
لقد اعتذرت لك. لماذا لا تزال تتجنبني؟
I'm not.
أنا لست كذلك.
Do whatever you want. I don't care!
افعل ما تريد. لا أهتم!
The number you have dialed is temporarily unanswered.
الرقم الذي طلبته لا يتم الرد عليه مؤقتا.
Please dial again later.
يرجى الاتصال مرة أخرى في وقت لاحق.
Auntie, let me clean the place.
عمتي، اسمحوا لي أن تنظيف المكان.
That was exhausting.
كان ذلك مرهقًا.
Jing Zhixia, forgive me.
جينغ زيكسيا، اغفر لي.
Fu Zeyi, are you sick or something?
فو زيي، هل أنت مريض أو شيء من هذا؟
I don't need another coaster.
لا أحتاج لسفينة أخرى.
Jing Zhixia, I'm sorry. Can we meet?
جينغ زيكسيا، أنا آسف. أيمكن أن نلتقي؟
♫ Once again, my love life has infinite opportunities ♫
♫ مرة أخرى، حياتي العاطفية لديها فرص لا حصر لها ♫
Fine. I won't drive. I'm taking the subway.
بخير. لن أقود. أنا آخذ المترو.
Seriously?
بجد؟
[Jing Zhixia, I'm sorry. Give me another chance!]
[جينغ زيكسيا، أنا آسف. أعطني فرصة أخرى!]
♫ Once again, my love life has infinite opportunities ♫
♫ مرة أخرى، حياتي العاطفية لديها فرص لا حصر لها ♫
♫ Our love has been engraved deep in my heart ♫
♫ حبنا محفور بعمق في قلبي ♫
♫ In the end, we're no longer together ♫
♫ في النهاية، لم نعد معًا ♫
♫ In the end, we've become a pair of strangers ♫
♫ في النهاية، أصبحنا زوجًا من الغرباء ♫
Sorry.
آسف.
It's you!
إنه أنت!
Listen. Your posters are blocking my posters.
يستمع. ملصقاتك تمنع ملصقاتي.
Do you owe him money or something? The posters are everywhere!
هل أنت مدين له بالمال أو شيء من هذا؟ الملصقات في كل مكان!
I don't know how to explain this.
لا أعرف كيف أشرح هذا.
By the way, what are you doing here?
بالمناسبة ماذا تفعل هنا؟
I'm here for your mother's wedding.
أنا هنا لحضور حفل زفاف والدتك.
My mother's wedding?
زفاف والدتي؟
I am Ye Ming's younger brother.
أنا الأخ الأصغر ليي مينغ.
From now on, we are family.
من الآن فصاعدا، نحن عائلة.
I hope we get along.
آمل أن نتفق.
If you ever need help, ask away.
إذا كنت بحاجة إلى مساعدة في أي وقت، اسأل بعيدا.
I do need your help with something now.
أنا بحاجة لمساعدتكم في شيء ما الآن.
How polite of you to ask.
كم هو مهذب منك أن تسأل.
You finally agreed to see me.
لقد وافقت أخيرا على رؤيتي.
Don't you have things to tell me?
أليس لديك أشياء لتخبرني بها؟
You may tell me now.
يمكنك أن تقول لي الآن.
Okay.
تمام.
Listen carefully. I wasn't going to marry He Bei'er.
استمع بعناية. لم أكن أنوي الزواج من هي بيير.
I only wanted to mess with you to see if you still cared about me.
أردت فقط العبث معك لمعرفة ما إذا كنت لا تزال تهتم بي.
You know how I feel for you.
أنت تعرف كيف أشعر بالنسبة لك.
From what I see, you are confessing your love and want to reconcile.
مما أرى أنك تعترفين بحبك وتريدين المصالحة.
Can I take that as a yes?
هل يمكنني أن أعتبر ذلك نعم؟
I asked you out to make things clear with you.
لقد طلبت منك الخروج لتوضيح الأمور معك.
I have a boyfriend now.
لدي صديق الآن.
No way.
مستحيل.
You know him.
أنت تعرفه.
I know him?
أنا أعرفه؟
Fine.
بخير.
Bring him here.
أحضره إلى هنا.
It's been too long, Fu Zeyi.
لقد مضى وقت طويل جدًا، فو زيي.
What now?
ماذا الآن؟
Are you going to break your promise?
هل ستخلف وعدك؟
Well, that's the power of love.
حسنًا، هذه هي قوة الحب.
Drop the act.
إسقاط الفعل.
You'd never fall for a man like him.
لن تقعي أبداً في حب رجل مثله.
What kind of man do you prefer then?
أي نوع من الرجال تفضلين إذن؟
Don't be so sure.
لا تكن متأكدا من ذلك.
People change.
الناس يتغيرون.
Besides, I don't think Xia Xia would fall for a man like you either.
علاوة على ذلك، لا أعتقد أن شيا شيا ستقع في حب رجل مثلك أيضًا.
Fine.
بخير.
Tell me,
أخبرني،
what does she like about you?
ماذا تحب فيك؟
That question is such a cliché.
هذا السؤال هو مثل هذه الكليشيهات.
That's between Xia Xia and me.
هذا بيني وبين شيا شيا.
I prefer not to share it with outsiders.
أفضّل عدم مشاركتها مع الغرباء.
You've met him. Would you please leave now?
لقد التقيت به. هلا غادرت الآن؟
What should I do to a conversation with you?
ماذا يجب أن أفعل للمحادثة معك؟
Perhaps you should attend our wedding.
ربما يجب عليك حضور حفل زفافنا.
And...
و...
would you please leave that seat?
هلا تركت هذا المقعد من فضلك؟
I prefer sitting in front of her to admire her beauty.
أفضّل الجلوس أمامها لأعجب بجمالها.
You can find an actor but find a capable one at least.
يمكنك العثور على ممثل ولكن العثور على ممثل قادر على الأقل.
I dare you to say that again.
أتحداك أن تقول ذلك مرة أخرى.
Jing Zhixia, what are you up to?
جينغ زيكسيا، ماذا تفعل؟
Do you still not believe it?
هل ما زلت لا تصدق ذلك؟
Bring it on.
اجلبه.
- What should I bring? - What do you think?
- ماذا يجب أن أحضر؟ - ماذا تعتقد؟
Seriously?
بجد؟
Fine.
بخير.
I'll leave.
سأغادر.
Wait.
انتظر.
I'm not done with you.
أنا لم انتهي معك.
I hope we don't meet again.
أتمنى ألا نلتقي مرة أخرى.
I don't want to ever see you again.
لا أريد أن أراك مرة أخرى.
I think we overdid it.
أعتقد أننا بالغنا في ذلك.
Any sensible person can tell he's in love with you.
يمكن لأي شخص عاقل أن يخبرك أنه يحبك.
Does it matter?
هل يهم؟
Would you want to be with a liar?
هل تريد أن تكون مع كاذب؟
Perhaps we shouldn't have met each other in the very beginning.
ربما لم يكن علينا أن نلتقي ببعضنا البعض في البداية.
♫  There's not a day that I'm afraid to be alone  ♫
♫ ليس هناك يوم أخاف فيه أن أكون وحدي ♫
♫  I’m afraid of seeing you again after we said our goodbyes  ♫
♫ أخشى رؤيتك مرة أخرى بعد أن قلنا وداعنا ♫
♫  I'm slowly getting used to missing you  ♫
♫ لقد اعتدت ببطء على اشتياقي لك ♫
♫  It seems like I've locked my heart away as the memory lingers  ♫
♫يبدو أنني قد أغلقت قلبي بعيدًا بينما تبقى الذكرى ♫
♫  If I decide to be brave this time  ♫
♫ إذا ​​قررت أن أكون شجاعاً هذه المرة ♫
♫  Then I'll hold your hands till eternity  ♫
♫ إذًا سأمسك يديك إلى الأبد ♫
♫  The moment we found the emotions we'd lost,  ♫
♫ في اللحظة التي وجدنا فيها المشاعر التي فقدناها، ♫
♫  we will overcome those lonely moments little by little  ♫
♫ سوف نتغلب على لحظات الوحدة تلك شيئاً فشيئاً ♫
♫  If you were by my side  ♫
♫ لو كنت بجانبي ♫
♫  No matter how many promises we've broken  ♫
♫ بغض النظر عن عدد الوعود التي نكثناها ♫
♫  There's nothing I'm not willing to do  ♫
♫ لا يوجد شيء لست على استعداد لفعله ♫
♫  in order to have a simple and ordinary life with you  ♫
♫ لكي أحظى بحياة بسيطة وعادية معك ♫
♫  If you were by my side  ♫
♫ لو كنت بجانبي ♫
♫  All my regrets will be blown away by the wind  ♫
♫ كل ما أشعر به من ندم سوف تتطايره الريح ♫
♫  I only want you to be with me every second, every minute  ♫
♫ أريدك فقط أن تكون معي في كل ثانية، كل دقيقة ♫